<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Akhil</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/</link><description>Recent content on Akhil</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 20:15:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akhilerm.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 6 blind men</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/the-six-blind-men/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 20:15:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/the-six-blind-men/</guid><description>NOTE This story has an abrupt ending because I woke up suddenly in the middle of the night.
Characters:
Akhil (myself) Gagan Scene 1 There exists a large corporation that deals with lot of businesses and investments. It is headed by 6 men who are blind. Nobody knows the complete whereabouts of these men, but it is rumoured that they are like a board and one of them is the chairman.</description></item><item><title>The real reason why Elon Musk built reusable rockets</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/real-reason-why-elon-musk-built-reusable-rockets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:31:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/real-reason-why-elon-musk-built-reusable-rockets/</guid><description>Warning This is a work of fiction, or to rephrase it better, a work of my subconscious mind. It might seem a little different from my previous blog posts about my dreams, since I have reordered certain scenes, as I felt that makes better sense for the complete story.
Characters:
Akhil Elon Musk Scene 1 I was at the SpaceX rocket building site, observing how the rockets were built.</description></item><item><title>A Lucy During Lockdown</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/a-lucy-during-lockdown/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:31:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/a-lucy-during-lockdown/</guid><description>Warning This is a work of fiction, or better a work of my subconscious mind. I have tried my level best to recollect the scenes from the dream and put it across. But still, the direction of story may change unexpectedly, scenes may have abrupt cuts and the story may resemble movies that I have watched.
Characters:
Akhil Vishnu Sr.Rosily and the actors Jake Gyllenhaal Adam Sandler Cliff Curtis Scene 1 A movie screening is going on in the auditorium of my higher secondary school which is mostly empty.</description></item><item><title>OpenEBS NDM, go-to solution for managing Kubernetes Local Storage</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/openebs-ndm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 19:27:53 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/openebs-ndm/</guid><description/></item><item><title>From Egypt to London via Kottayam</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/egypt-kottayam-london/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 20:15:25 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/egypt-kottayam-london/</guid><description>Warning This is a work of fiction, or better a work of my subconscious mind. I have tried my level best to recollect the scenes from the dream and put it across. But still, the direction of story may change unexpectedly, scenes may have abrupt cuts and the story may resemble movies that I have watched.
Characters:
Akhil (myself) Jeswin Scene 1 The world is dying and there are huge wars being fought everywhere across the globe.</description></item><item><title>Uniquely identifying disks in OpenEBS on VMWare platform</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/openebs-unique-disks-vmware/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 19:19:06 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/openebs-unique-disks-vmware/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Creating manual BlockDevice in OpenEBS</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/create-manual-blockdevice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 19:17:03 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/create-manual-blockdevice/</guid><description/></item><item><title>OpenEBS Node Device Management (NDM) - Troubleshooting tips</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/ndm-troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 19:14:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/ndm-troubleshooting/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Configuring OpenEBS to run with Security-Enhanced Linux</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/configure-openebs-selinux/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 19:06:46 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/configure-openebs-selinux/</guid><description/></item><item><title>My First Skydive experience.</title><link>https://akhilerm.com/posts/my-first-skydive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:14:55 +0400</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/posts/my-first-skydive/</guid><description>Everything you love is on the other side of maximum fear Skydive Dubai is known for its safest tandem jump with an awesome view of Palm Jumeirah, though a bit expensive compared to other Drop zones. Skydiving was one of the activity that I had decided to do before I leave Dubai. And today I did it.
Me and my collegue Jesvin (who also happens to be my Team lead at office :D) made bookings in Skydive Dubai for the morning slot at 10:45 AM.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://akhilerm.com/portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/portfolio/</guid><description>OpenSource Contributions 🌐🖥️ OpenEBS: Maintainer of OpenEBS disk management plane and local storage options Docker / Moby: Fixes related to accessing devices in privileged mode diskfs: Fix for creating partitions on disk Seagate: Bug fix for NVMe device and memory corruption Google Container Tools, Google: Added support for new method in golang github API Azure Kubesphere ⚠️ Sign in to github to view complete list of contributions.
Talks 👨🎤 2021 Container Attached Storage 101 @ CNCF Bangalore Meetup Heterogeneous CSI Drivers @ OpenSource India 2019 Kubernetes stateful workloads on legacy storage @ DevConf India Contributing to open source @ Hacktoberfest Bangalore Meetup Personal Projects 👨 2022 Eywa 💳 : Service to generate UPI payment request for pending splitwise balance.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://akhilerm.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://akhilerm.com/projects/</guid><description>Personal 👨 2021 Tag-Push github action📦🐬 : Github Action to retag and push multiplatform container images to multiple remote registries. 2018 Dooth 📱 : A secret messenger for Amazon Alexa.
Easy Dialer 📞🇦🇪 : A calling card automation app to be used in UAE.
2017 Castle 🏰 : An open source implementation of the famous Google foobar challenge. Built out of inspiration from friends who couldn&amp;rsquo;t secure an invitation to the challenge.</description></item></channel></rss>